[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 30]
We've been in here too long.
We have to find the crack as soon as possible.
I'm afraid
we won't be able to get out later.
I'm affected by Yin-yang Power.
I can't use the water spirit.
Luo Ge.
I can only count on you.
If the Immortal does something,
the boundary can be barely opened
for a moment.
They're coming.
I'll go stop them first.
Shiwei.
Luo Ge, what should we do?
He Na.
You go first.
Hurry.
Okay.
Luo Ge.
Come on out.
What are you doing?
Luo Ge, what do you mean?
He Na.
Take care of Liu Shao for me.
Luo Ge.
I have to stay here to cleanse the evil spirit.
Luo Ge!
The poison is finally gone.
But if Liu Shao wakes up,
I'm sure she'll ask to save Luo Ge.
I'm injured now.
I can't help them.
Brother.
You're injured again?
What's so good about that Liu Shao?
She's gotten you into trouble again and again.
Luo Ning came here.
Mr. Tai told you?
I can't let her see you come back.
If she knows
Luo Ge is still in Yin-yang Cave,
I'm afraid she'll make it a big deal.
She's Luo Ge's sister.
There are some things
she should know.
If Luo Ge dies today,
it can only be good for us.
Fu.
The Three Realms are inextricably linked.
If something happens to Luo Ge,
it can't be good for the demon world.
Even if it's for Luo Ning's sake,
you shouldn't let her down.
Why not?
Luo Ge is the stumbling block
for us to break free.
You're always like this.
I'm afraid you'll regret it one day.
I see.
This is the medicine I had Mr. Tai recently make.
It should be good for your hand.
Immortal.
Your immortal energy is already damaged.
You don't have to stay for us.
We're all disciples of the Immortal Palace.
I won't give up on you.
And the evil spirit in the cave can affect the Four Seasons Monument at any time.
Only by setting up a formation with my immortal energy
can I purify the resentment of the fellow disciples
at once.
It's also my wish.
I'm willing to do my small part.
I've already found her.
My wish has been fulfilled.
I don't
ask for your protection.
If you need me,
I would kill or die for you.
What are you talking about?
You're a righteous man
of honor.
The Immortal will protect you.
I'm ashamed to say
that I...
Since you want to help,
why don't we split up
and set up the formation with my immortal energy?
Xie Lingqi.
You've been guarding the Three Realms for a thousand years.
It's a blessing for the Immortal Palace.
You have to do a lot more
for the Immortal Palace in the future.
I will complete whatever I'm entrusted with.
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao.
He Na.
Where is Luo Ge?
He stayed in the cave.
He said he had to purify the evil spirit
and let us out first.
I've unblocked
the restraint Bai Feng placed on the Wang Bell.
Luo Ge.
Luo Ge, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why didn't you come out?
You don't have to worry.
I'm staying here
to resolve
the resentment of the disciples of the Immortal Palace.
You should rest well.
Don't worry about me.
Is it because you're affected by our incompatible spiritual power?
Anyway,
no matter what,
you'll come out.
You will definitely come out, right?
What if
I can't get out
and I'm trapped here?
Will you wait for me?
If you can't get out,
I'll get married to another guy.
How dare you?
So consider it for my sake,
come out, please.
Okay.
I will.
You're leaving?
If you're going to Yin-yang Cave,
can you wait for me for a couple of days?
I'll go with you
after a short rest.
Although you won't tell me,
I know you're badly hurt.
Just stay here and recuperate.
But you…
Don't worry.
I won't act impulsively.
I will go back to the Immortal Palace
and ask the seniors for help.
That's good.
The one who sealed the cave
was Shang Yurong's father,
Lord Shang.
Go to Shang Yurong.
He will help you.
Okay.
No matter what,
I will get Luo Ge out of there.
You will.
Master Shang, Immortal Master.
Liu Shao.
Do you recognize your fault?
I don't understand.
You promised not to see Luo Ge again.
Not only did you break your promise,
you even got Luo Ge into the Ying-yang Cave.
Now that you're out,
why hasn't he come out yet?
He...
Luo Ge just sent me a message,
saying he had to
purify the evil spirit in the Ying-yang Cave.
He can take it as a cultivation
which can also
stabilizes the Four Seasons Monument.
Nonsense.
If no one had broken into the cave,
there would not be any evil spirit turmoil.
If Luo Ge's cultivation is damaged again this time,
can you afford the responsibility, Liu Shao?
Let's go to the Ying-yang Cave.
We have to get Luo Ge out as soon as possible.
The Tian Kui Formation I asked you to set up
can eliminate all the evil spirit
within the area covered by the formation.
After the center is set up,
Tian Kui Formation
will activate itself in one hour.
It's finally done.
Shiwei.
See if there's an antidote on these people.
I found it.
Lingqi.
Shiwei.
This is the fourth bottle we found.
You're good.
Let's go meet up with Luo Ge.
Let's go.
Okay.
What's wrong with you?
Let's go.
Don't scare me.
Wake up.
I'm Lingqi.
I just...
Shiwei.
Your will is stronger than others.
And you've practiced mind-clearing cultivation.
That's why you've been able to
barely keep sober.
But...
But I've been here for a thousand years.
The Moon Poison has already penetrated my bones.
It can't be eradicated.
I could lose my mind at any time,
or even harm those around me.
Right?
You can collect more Sun Spring.
You only need a small amount to recover
with your physical state.
I'm not afraid.
I'm happy
to see you again.
Even if I have to go back…
Don't say that.
Immortal Luo Ge is here.
We will be fine.
It's okay.
I won't leave you here alone again
this time.
Liu Shao.
Why are you here?
I know your immortal energy is damaged.
I brought an expert to help you.
An expert?
Luo Ge.
You should be recuperating at Place Chonghua.
Why are you back?
And with an expert?
Luo Ge.
Could you expect
that you need me to save you one day?
Shang Yurong.
I'm afraid your Burning Sea
is not enough.
We still got a fairy here, right?
Liu Shao.
Stand back.
Burning Sea?
I thought he didn't acquire it after hundreds of years of practice.
Shang Yurong acquired it
500 years ago.
Watch out.
They're coming after us.
They've been trapped here for a thousand years.
It's their obsession to get out.
As long as there's a loophole in the boundary,
they will do whatever it takes to escape.
Immortal.
You're wounded.
Let us do it.
Liu Shao.
Attack the rift.
Even the Lightning Slash can't break it.
Liu Shao.
Do you have any other moves?
If you do,
use it.
Help me.
Liu Shao.
Inject Qi into your body and help the yin with the yang.
Bodhi palms together, hand-knotted with a flower.
Hide the hollowness of Taixu, and make your mind fall into the sea of Qi.
The heart moves with the hands and the music of heaven comes out.
This is the power of the Sun.
Luo Ge.
Come out.
Help me maintain the boundary crack.
Xie Lingqi, come out!
Shiwei.
Go!
Come back!
I can't hold on anymore.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Shiwei.
Shiwei!
Lingqi.
You don't have to wait for me this time.
Shiwei.
♫The begonia is red, but every promise makes it more withered♫
♫It blooms alone, but the wind and rain are more violent♫
Don't worry about me, you go first, it's too late.
♫Plants are not human beings, and ruthless fruits are planted♫
I won't leave you here.
-Let's go together. -Just go.
♫How can you forget the innocence and ignorance when we first met?♫
Shiwei.
♫The butterfly emerges from the chrysalis, but it is difficult to fly to the sky♫
Immortal.
I beg you.
Shiwei is still inside.
♫The butterfly's wings were broken, and the dream fell without a trace♫
Help me get her out, please.
I just found her.
Help me get her out!
♫Because of their greed for the warmth of fire, they lost each other♫
She's not dead yet.
She's still inside.
Help me get her out.
♫There is a period of youth, and he is waiting for the spring breeze in the coming year♫
She's still in there.
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
She's still in there.
I beg you.
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
I beg you.
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
She's still in there.
♫I'm willing to spread my wings♫
♫And don't fight the fate♫
I'm sorry.
♫It's a good moment to share the world with you♫
I can't save her.
But Shiwei
saved all the fellow disciples.
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
Shiwei.
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
I'll go plead for General Xie
in front of senior.
I hope she'll lighten his punishment.
Okay.
Xie Lingqi.
If you don't mind,
you can stay at Palace Chonghua first.
I will explain everything
to Master Zhuo.
That's not necessary.
In Shiwei's mind,
I'm a righteous
and responsible man.
I can't let her down.
I will return to the Bone Melting Pool from today.
I will be punished
as I should be
for the wrong I have done.
This is the Sun Spring
I've collected with Shiwei these days.
Now she
won't use it anymore.
So take it
as our token of appreciation.
You can use it for your health.
Take it as the least contribution
Shiwei did
for all beings in the Three Realms.
Thank you, General Yu.
My condolences.
Luo Ge.
If I were trapped for a thousand years,
would you
never give up looking for me
like Xie Lingqi did?
I can't bear
to let you be trapped for a thousand years either.
The pain of a thousand years of departure is unbearable.
So I want to find
the way to eliminate the conflict of spiritual powers.
But the fragments of Sun Spirit
have been fused with you.
I will find another way for you.
I have to seal the spirit energy as soon as possible.
I can't let Luo Ge get hurt for me again.
Luo Ge is out?
Yes.
Shang Yurong, Master of the Three Palaces,
saved Luo Ge from death
with the Burning Sea.
I never thought he would be so lucky.
The Immortal is safe and sound.
You can return to the Immortal Palace at any time
to reunite with him.
Your injury...
It's just a minor injury.
It's nothing to worry about.
If you're not treated in time,
will it
be dangerous?
You don't have to bother, Fairy Luo Ning.
Bone-corroding Harp?
Fairy.
If you are willing to help me,
can you lift the curse of Aquatic Demons?
I...
Can I do it?
Legend has it that Immortal Ze Shui
can lift the curse
with the Bone-corroding Harp.
You should be the successor of Immortal Ze Shui's immortal energy.
If you are willing to do so,
I'd like you to give it a try.
Okay.
Bone-corroding Harp.
Luo Ning.
Demon King.
I'm afraid
I can't lift the curse.
As I thought about lifting the curse,
my hands got powerless.
Maybe it's because
someone doesn't think
I'm qualified.
Even the inheritor of Immortal Ze Shui
can't break the curse?
Tell me.
I'm coming back like nothing happened.
What should I say
to the Immortal Master?
No need to explain.
I have something to discuss with you.
Liu Shao, you're finally back.
Is it cold in the house?
I'll go back first.
Liu Shao.
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Master.
I want to seal the divine spirit.
I need your help to do so.
Luo Ning.
Your brother has left the Ying-yang Cave
and is back at the Immortal Palace.
I know.
Your brother has just told me.
My brother?
Yes.
He cares about your brother.
Why are you here again?
I was thinking about
the curse of your clan.
Since it's caused by
the Demon King and Immortal Ze Shui,
I think
the Brahma Tree
should know something.
But
I can feel the presence of the tree spirit.
I can also feel
it's very friendly to me.
But it just won't say anything to me.
Anyway, the curse
has been trapping us for 10,000 years.
No matter what,
I will
get rid of it.
Don't take the wrong path.
I'll listen to you.
I won't take the wrong path.
Okay?
You're just saying that.
But you don't think that way at all.
Am I right?
That's not true.
You're watching over me,
aren't you?
Does it help?
Even if I'm watching you,
will you listen to me?
Can I clear your bad thoughts?
All right.
I'm going back to the Immortal Palace.
Why do you have to go back again?
I think your brother
is also worried about this every day.
Since this is caused by
Immortal Ze Shui,
I, as the inheritor of her immortal energy,
should have a chance to solve this.
I'm thinking about
asking my brother
and those
elders in the Immortal Palace.
Maybe there will be some clues.
It's about the Aquatic Demons.
What's the point of asking a bunch of old men
in the Immortal Palace?
I'll take care of the demon realm.
Why don't you
just be a happy little fairy?
No.
Who knows what other crazy things you'll do
to lift the curse?
Okay, that's it.
I'm really going back.
I forbid you to go.
Who knows
when you'll be back?
You forbid me?
How?
You're locking me up
and won't let me go out?
No.
Fu.
Remember.
You're not the Demon King from 10,000 years ago.
I'm not Immortal Ze Shui either.
So
don't always think of imitating the Demon King,
understand?
Yes, I understand.
Whether you find the way or not,
you have to promise me one thing.
Don't come back too late to see me.
Three days.
Five days.
Seven days.
It depends on my mood.
At least give me a message.
Half a month at most.
Don't leave me for a long time.
What little fairy?
She's a little witch.
She comes and goes
whenever she likes.
What does she take me for?
What a princess!
Mother of Trees.
You're treating me like this too.
I can chop you up and burn you as firewood.
The Mother of Trees
is also a princess
like Luo Ning.
Now she's gone.
I wonder how long it will take for her to return.
No way.
I must marry her.
When she comes next time,
I'll make her happy first
and then talk to my brother about it.
That's it.
So you asked us to come here
to nourish
Liu Shao's body?
Yes.
She only has one talisman pearl left in her body.
And all that she's been through
has affected her cultivation.
So
I want your help.
Maybe you can see something that I can't.
Even if it's just
a little clue.
You're being overly greedy.
Her spiritual power has been damaged.
It's difficult to cultivate again.
Do you want to spoil it?
But
if you stew him,
Liu Shao's cultivation level can rise by at least one or two steps.
Think twice about it, Immortal.
Don't look at me like that.
Master.
You've lived for 10,000 years.
That's about right.
Immortal.
Master.
I remember how good you are to Liu Shao.
Immortal.
Remember to burn some ghost money for me
on festivals.
Gold dollars would do too.
Prepare the medicine on the list.
Maybe you won't need the ghost money.
You might as well stew me up.
The Immortal Master scolded Master Shang.
Immortal Luo broke into the Ying-yang Cave.
My “Anecdote of the Xiyin Mountain”
is further enriched.
Liu Shao.
You're still thinking about sealing the divine energy?
I already have the Tears of the Half-Demon.
What I don't have now is
the assistance of three immortals whose cultivation is above the general.
Shang Yurong is easy to deal with.
But I don't know
how to convince Master Zhuo.
It's simple.
Why don't you let Shang Yurong do it for you?
Zhuo Qiuqin has been very nice to Shang Yurong these days.
You won't
really seal the divine energy
for the Immortal, will you?
It will only make him worry
if I tell him I plan to do it.
Forget it.
Master.
The Immortal asks to see you.
You are
always tormenting me.
What medicines are still missing?
What are you rushing for?
I've never even seen
some of them before.
Baffling Star Stone.
Clear Vine.
See?
Where can I find it for you?
Immortal Luo Ge.
These herbs are not just for health.
They can also enhance
Liu Shao's Sun Spirit.
Aren't you afraid
that it will make your spiritual power
even more incompatible?
Isn't the Clear Vine you mentioned
in the Bone Melting Pool?
Yes.
But it takes the power of a God to find it.
What about the Baffling Star Stone?
That's even harder to find.
That was the collection of the Demon King ten thousand years ago.
Demon King?
Immortal.
The Demon King requests an audience.
I thought you would meet me at Litian Temple
or at Palace Chonghua.
When Liu Shao and I were at our wit's end,
it was you who stood in front of us,
saying
we were your friends.
So you remembered.
I remembered after I ascended to immortality.
Lu Li's friend
is also my friend.
I hadn't mentioned it deliberately before.
But it's not because I forgot.
In fact,
I've always considered you my best friend too.
He Na.
Since you said we are friends,
there is no need to be polite.
If you have anything to say, say it.
[From the Demon King He Na]
The immortals and demons are bound to each other.
From now on, we will live in peace
with no more conflicts.
He Na.
That's a good wish.
Do you think it's improper?
I think it's good too.
And I hope that one day it will be so.
But there is Xie Lingqi in the Immortal Palace.
And so does the Demon Palace.
Someone at the Demon Palace caused trouble?
Xie Lingqi should be the only one who has
the Moon Poison Liu Shao suffers from.
From Xie Lingqi's hiding to Bai Feng's poisoning,
I suspect
someone passed it on.
You mean Fu?
You are the king of the demon realm.
If Fu makes a mistake,
how can you convince the people?
I see you as a friend.
But I can't give Fu a break
because of you.
I think you can understand that.
I understand.
There's one more thing I want to ask you.
What is it?
Just say it.
In the cave,
Liu Shao forced out
the divine weapon of the Sun, the Crown Wheel.
She should be able to inherit the power of the Sun soon.
So I want to find some herbs
to boost her divine energy.
and help with her cultivation.
Is there any medicine that is not available at the Immortal Palace?
Baffling Star Stone.
What's that?
The Brahma Tree is glowing.
It's...
His Majesty's Demon King's power.
Could it be that His Majesty
is searching for something
with his power as the Demon King?
He's actually using the spiritual power of Demon King.